#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/duy-thanhnguyen-ba-841508 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Office
Project Management
Microsoft Excel

# Cris Nguyen (Nguyen Ba Duy Thanh)

**Business Development Manager** 

Vietnam

# Summary

We specialize in the field of factory design and construction. With my experience and youth, I always want to bring the construction business community in Vietnam a fair competitive environment. Contributing to bring the country's construction industry to a worldclass level.

## Experience

#### MEGACON INDUSTRIAL CONSTRUCTION JSC

1 year 5 months

Business Director July 2024 - Present (9 months)

Hanoi Capital Region

Project Manager November 2023 - Present (1 year 5 months) Hanoi Capital Region

Ysl Group
Project Manager
July 2022 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Tcon Viet Nam
Director of Business Development
August 2021 - Present (3 years 8 months)
Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

#### **GDC GROUP**

Project Manager January 2021 - Present (4 years 3 months) Ha Noi FECON Group Project Manager March 2020 - December 2020 (10 months) Hanoi, Thành Phố Hà Nội, Vietnam

Kovicons Ltd Project Manager June 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 5 months) Hanoi

Bitexco Group of Companies Senior Construction Supervisor March 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 11 months) Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Phuc Hung Holding Construction Joint Stock Company Deputy of Project Manager April 2012 - May 2016 (4 years 2 months) Ha Noi, Viet Nam

## Education

Columbia Southern University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Business/Commerce,

General · (2019 - 2020)

University of Communications and Transports VietNam Bachelor's degree, Roads and Bridges · (2002 - 2007)